>> Brian Holt: 我们将在这里再创建一个文件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We are going
to create one more file here.
这将会是一个 gitignore 文件。
This is going to be a gitignore file.
因此，在源目录中，创建一个名为 .gitignore的文件。
So inside of your source directory,
create a file called .gitignore.
>> Brian Holt:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Like that.
不是在你的源头里
Not inside your source one,
这将会进入您的根目录中
this is going to go inside of your
root directory inside of adopt me.
> > Brian Holt: 如果你不熟悉，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
here if you are not familiar with get,
这才是说说的意思是这里有一堆东西
this is just telling get is like,
here is a bunch of stuff,
我不想让你跟踪我的忏悔
I don't want you to keep
a track of inside of my repo.
好吧那就用点吧
Okay, so .getignore yes use dot.
所以你第一次不想追踪的是节点模块
So the first thing you never
want to track is node modules,
因为这就是你晚上晚上可以安装的原因，对吧 ?
because that's why you can npm
install them wherever you want, right?
>> Brian Holt: 如果您在 Mac 上，您应该始终忽略 DS_Store，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then also if you're on
Mac you should always ignore DS_Store,
这是麦克为了愚蠢的原因而创造的文件让我们不要谈论它
which is a file that Mac creates for
dumb reasons, let's not talk about it.
我们就说这些都是愚蠢的原因
Let's just say that they're dumb reasons.
然后在接下来的过程中，你会忽略你的缓存。
And then for later parts of the course,
you're going to ignore your cache.
你会忽略 dist的
You're going to ignore dist.
你会忽略覆盖范围的
You're going to ignore coverage.
您可以忽略 dot VS Code 目录，也可以不忽略该目录。
You can ignore the dot VS Code
directory or not, that one's up to you.
就在 VS 代码记录下你个人喜好的项目上
It's just where VS Code keeps track of all
your personal preferences for the project,
然后你也会忽略 .emv 文件
and then you're also going
to ignore the .emv file.
所以这仅仅是对  的解释，忽略所有这些东西，从不承诺这些东西。
So this is just telling VS Code, ignore
all this stuff, never commit this stuff.
这就是我给我的东西，不给我放进去的东西
This is stuff that I just have for
me and not to be put in my get
repo >> Brian Holt: 好的，
repo
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
所以这里还有一个 commit point 。
so there's another commit point here.
所以如果你在工装后面摔下来，你就可以跳下去了
So if you fell people behind the tooling
you can feel free to just jump up to
这个承诺。
this commit.
这就像添加 npm 脚本和 ES Lint 和 prettier 一样
It's something called like add npm
scripts and ES Lint and prettier and
就像这样
things like that.